<Jose Posadas/>

Junior software developer

8085 Caminito de Pizza San Diego, Ca

Professional Summary

Junior software developer with a diverse background in the Specialty Coffee industry. Experienced in various roles such as entrepreneur, manager, and owner-operator of a retail coffee business with international locations. Recently completed the UC Davis software developer BootCamp. Strong problem-solving skills, adaptability, and creativity. Able to bring a unique perspective to software development and contribute to the success of any team.

Employment history

FORT MYERS FLORIDA 2022 - 2023

E-COMMERCE MANAGER, Trek Bikes of Florida

- Managed online sales for Trek Bikes of Florida, overseeing online retail for their 19 locations in Florida
- Developed and managed online operations, including tracking inventory and shipping from vendors
- Provided customer support and troubleshooting for the website and software

OAKLAND CALIFORNIA 2020 - 2022

QUALITY CONTROL TECHNICIAN, GROUND CONTROL

- Implement and maintain a comprehensive quality control program to ensure the highest standards of product quality and consistency in all aspects of the coffee brewing equipment manufacturing process.
- Develop and maintain quality control processes and procedures for commercial coffee brewing equipment.
- Conduct regular audits and inspections to identify areas for improvement in the quality control program and recommend appropriate corrective actions.

OAKLAND CALIFORNIA 2014 - 2021

MANAGING PARTNER, COLOSO COFFEE

- Created and implemented workflow for retail and wholesale roasting operations
- Expanded the brand internationally and grew to 3 locations
- Managed business operations and served as a mentor and trainer for staff.
- Identifying and analyzing market trends to drive business growth and identify new opportunities

Education

JUN, 2023 - NOV, 2023 Coding Bootcamp at UC Davis

2010 - 2012

AA Graphic Design, City College of San Francisco

Studied graphic design history and principles. Experimented in printing and photography. Trained in digital design and photo retouching.

Links

Github Profile Linkedin